Guide to the Freedom to Marry Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Program Files, 1973-2016; Series IV; 45.84; 113 boxes
  - Publications, 1973-2015
    - Redbook Magazine, 2006 (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Same-Sex Couples: Marriage, Families and Children, 1999 December (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - Same-Sex Marriage, Gay Rights and the Counter Mobilization of the Law, 2000 August-September (Box 78, Folder 15)
    - San Francisco Chronicle magazine, 2007 July 1 (Box 78, Folder 16)
    - Spanish translation (Box 78, Folder 17)
    - State of the States: Report from the Federation Marriage Summit of the States, 2004 May (Box 78, Folder 18)
    - To Have To Hold: Organizing for Our Right to Marry, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 19)
    - Trial magazine, 1993 July (Box 78, Folder 20)
    - Variety Marriage Equality and the Supreme Court, 2015 June 29 (Box 78, Folder 21)
    - Voter ID Institute: How to Win Campaigns That Matter to Our Community, 1999 November 11 (Box 78, Folder 22)
    - Website, 2013-2015
    - Why Marriage Matters Campaign (Box 78, Folder 23)
    - Widener Law Journal Marriage, Equality and America: Committed Couples, Committed Lives, 2004 (Box 78, Folder 24)
    - William and Mary Journal of Women and the Law volume 12 issue 3, 2006 Spring (Box 78, Folder 25)
    - Winning Marriage book pamphlet (Box 78, Folder 26)
    - Working With the Press, 2005 (Box 78, Folder 27)
  - Internet and social media, 2006-2015
    - Facebook account, 2008-2018
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      http://wayback.archive-it.org/6622/20170620102456/https://www.facebook.com/freedomtomarry.org
      Immediate Source of Acquisition
      Captured using the Archive-It service on 20 June 2017
    - Instagram account
      http://wayback.archive-it.org/6622/20151207150635/http://www.instagram.com/freedomtomarry
    - Tumblr account
      http://wayback.archive-it.org/6622/20170619131429/https://freedomtomarry.tumblr.com
    - Twitter account, 2008-2018
      http://wayback.archive-it.org/6622/20170619133817/https://twitter.com/freedomtomarry
    - Website, 2006-2015
      http://wayback.archive-it.org/6598/20171127154233/http://freedomtomarry.org
      Captured using the Archive-It service on 23 January 2018
    - Youtube account, 2006-2015
      http://wayback.archive-it.org/6622/20170619131428/https://www.youtube.com/user/FreedomToMarry/videos
- Regrant Files, 2001-2009; Series V; 2.04; 7 boxes
  This series is restricted until 2035 and may only be accessed with permission from the donor per the collection's deed of gift.
  The Regrant Files series consists of grant applications from partner organizations to Freedom to Marry. These files are almost exclusively grant applications and do not contain additional information about the partner organizations. Regranting material that includes additional information about partner organizations can be found in the Partner organization subseries of the Program Files series.
  The Regrant Files series is organized chronologically.
  - Gill Foundation, 2001 September (Box 161, Folder 1)
  - 2003-B Connecticut-Massachusetts Joint polling place, March 2002-May 2004 (Box 161, Folder 2)
  - 2003-A Gay and Lesbian Advocates and Defenders marriage project, 2003 March-2005 April (Box 161, Folder 3)
  - 2003-G Claiming the Blessing, 2002-2003 (Box 161, Folder 4)
  - Regranting grid, 2003 April-2005 November (Box 161, Folder 5)
  - Regranting committee meeting notes, 2003 April (Box 161, Folder 6)
  - 2003-D Lambda Legal New Jersey, 2003 April-2004 January (Box 161, Folder 7)
  - Regranting Washington, 2003-2004 (Box 161, Folder 8)
  - California, June 2003 retreat, 2003 June (Box 161, Folder 9)
  - 2003-C PFLAG-New Jersey Poll-Bergen couty, 2003 June-2005 January (Box 161, Folder 10)
  - 2003-E California Freedom to Marry Coalition, 2003 July (Box 161, Folder 11)
  - Lambda, Empire State Pride Agenda, MECA, 2003 August (Box 161, Folder 12)
  - 2003-F Marriage Equality California, 2003 December (Box 161, Folder 13)
  - Wisconsin: Action Wisconsin 2003-04, 2004 January (Box 161, Folder 14)
  - Equality forum 2004, 2004 March (Box 161, Folder 15)
  - 2004 general: Parents, Families, and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (PFLAG) Seattle, 2004 May-2004 June; 1 (Box 161, Folder 16, Box 165)
    - The Wedding Party, 2016-M-0049-0027; 1 (Box 165)
  - 2004 General Center for Lesbian and Gay Studies Pacific School of Religion, 2004 June (Box 161, Folder 17)
  - 2004 General Family Pride Coalition, 2004-2007 (Box 161, Folder 18)
  - Regranting process, 2004 July (Box 161, Folder 19)
  - 2006-J AFL-CIO Pride at work, 2005 April-2006 October (Box 161, Folder 20)
  - 2005-4 Equality Florida, 2005 June-2005 December (Box 161, Folder 21)
  - 2006-A Equality California Institute (coalition coordinator), 2005 May-2006 February (Box 161, Folder 22)
  - 2005-4 Equality Florida, 2005 June-2005 December (Box 161, Folder 23)
  - Common grant application, 2006 January (Box 161, Folder 24)
  - 2006-D Equal marriage matters Illinois, 2006 January (Box 161, Folder 25)
  - 2006-B Marriage equality matters, 2006 June (Box 161, Folder 26)
  - 2006-C Empire State Pride Agenda 2006 stateside poll, 2006 March-2006 April (Box 162, Folder 1)
  - 2006-G Empire State Pride Agenda, 2006 April (Box 162, Folder 2)
  - 2006-F One Iowa, 2006 April-2007 August (Box 162, Folder 3)
  - 2006-E National Black Justice Coalition, 2006 May (Box 162, Folder 4)
  - 2006-I Religious Coalition for Equality, 2006 May-2007; 1 (Box 162, Folder 5-6, Box 166)
    - Scripture & Marriage equality 2006 colloquy resource materials, 2016-M-0049-0028; 1 (Box 166)
  - Regranting, 2006 August-2006 November (Box 162, Folder 7)
  - 2006-H Garden state equality, 2006 August (Box 162, Folder 8)
  - Status reports, 2006 October-2006 November (Box 162, Folder 9)
  - 2006-K BREF, 2006 October (Box 162, Folder 10)
  - 2006-L Love Makes a Family, 2006 December (Box 162, Folder 11)
  - FTM Freedom to Marry week 2007 mini-grants, 2007 January-2007 February (Box 162, Folder 12)
  - 2007-A CalFUN, 2007 January (Box 162, Folder 13)
  - 2007-I National Black Justice Coalition Black church summit reimbursements, 2007 January-2007 April (Box 162, Folder 14)
  - 2007-I National Black Justice Coalition Travel/Black church summit, 2007 January-2007 April (Box 162, Folder 15)
  - 2007-3 affirmations, 2007 January (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - 2007-4 Atticus circle, 2007 January (Box 163, Folder 2)
  - 2007-5 Carolina Rainbow Family Coalition, 2007 February (Box 163, Folder 3)
  - 2007-6 Equal Rights Washington, 2007 January-2007 February (Box 163, Folder 4)
  - 2007-7 Equality Maryland, 2007 January-2007 February (Box 163, Folder 5)
  - 2006-I National Latino Coalition for Justice, 2007 January (Box 163, Folder 6)
  - 2007-08 Ithaca College, 2007 January (Box 163, Folder 7)
  - 2007-9 Marriage Equality Rhode Island, 2007 January (Box 163, Folder 8)
  - 2007-10 Marriage Equality USA, 2007 January (Box 163, Folder 9)
  - 2007-11 Oklahomans for Equality, 2007 January (Box 163, Folder 10)
  - 2007-12 Pennsylvania Diversity Network, 2007 January (Box 163, Folder 11)
  - 2007-13 Southern Colorado Equality Alliance, 2007 January (Box 163, Folder 12)
  - 2007-14 Spectrum, 2007 January (Box 163, Folder 13)
  - 2007-16 Wyoming Equality, 2007 January (Box 163, Folder 14)
  - 2007-E Vermont Freedom to Marry task force, 2007 January-2008 May (Box 163, Folder 15)
  - 2007-B South Carolina Coalition Foundation, 2007 February-2007 April (Box 163, Folder 16)
  - 2007-15 Student coalition for equality, 2007 February-2007 March (Box 163, Folder 17)
  - 2007-18 Equality Maine, 2007 February (Box 163, Folder 18)
  - 2007-K Love Makes a Family, 2007 March-2007 November (Box 163, Folder 19)
  - 2007-C California Equality Project, 2007 April (Box 163, Folder 20)
  - 2007-D Equality Maryland, 2007 April-2008 August (Box 163, Folder 21)
  - Equality Illinois, 2007 May (Box 163, Folder 22)
  - 2007-F Los Angeles Gay and Lesbian Center, 2007 May-2007 October (Box 163, Folder 23)
  - 2007-2 Amistad/Liberation conversations, 2007 May-2007 July (Box 163, Folder 24)
  - 2007-2 Amistad/Liberation conversations, 2007 May-2007 June (Box 163, Folder 25)
  - 2007-G Empire State Pride Agency, 2007 July-2007 August (Box 163, Folder 26)
  - 2007-G Empire State Pride Agency, 2007 July-2007 August (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - MassEquality Education Fund, 2007 September-2008 February (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - 2007-H Equality California Institute, 2007 September-2007 October (Box 164, Folder 3)
  - 2007-I Garden State Equality Educational Fund, 2007 September-2008 April (Box 164, Folder 4)
  - 2007-20 National collaborative, 2007 October (Box 164, Folder 5)
  - 2008-I National Collaborative, 2007 November (Box 164, Folder 6)
  - 2007-L National Black Justice Coalition (NBJC), 2007 November (Box 164, Folder 7)
  - Regranting information, 2008 January (Box 164, Folder 8)
  - 2008-A Equality Maine, 2008 March (Box 164, Folder 9)
  - 2008-2 National Black Justice Coalition (NBJC) partner support, 2008 April-2008 May (Box 164, Folder 10)
  - 2008-B Garden State Equality educational fund, 2008 May-2008 July (Box 164, Folder 11)
  - 2008-A National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) regrant, 2008 May-2009 April (Box 164, Folder 12)
  - 2008-C Empire State Pride Agenda Foundation, 2008 May-2008 June (Box 164, Folder 13)
  - Declined regrants, 2008 June (Box 164, Folder 14)
  - 2008-D And Castro for All, 2008 June (Box 164, Folder 15)
  - 2208-I Garden State Equality regrant, 2008 June-2009 February (Box 164, Folder 16)
  - 2008-4 Zuna Institute partner support, 2008 June-2008 October (Box 164, Folder 17)
  - 2008-E One Iowa regrant, 2008 August; 1 (Box 164, Folder 18, Box 167)
    - One Iowa 08-610 11/24/08, 2016-M-0049-0029; 1 (Box 167)
  - 2008-G National Black Justice Coalition (NBJC)/National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) regrant, 2008 August (Box 164, Folder 19)
  - 2008-H Equality Maine foundation, 2008 August-2008 November (Box 164, Folder 20)
  - 2008-J And Castro for All, 2008 December-2009 January (Box 164, Folder 21)
- Director of Public Engagement and Director of Research and Messaging Files, 2005-2015; Series VI; 3.75; 8 boxes
  The Director of Public Engagement and Director of Research and Messaging Files series cannot be accessed per the collection's deed of gifts until 1 January 2035.
  Boxes 168-174 cannot be accessed without permission from the donor.
  Box 175 cannot be accessed until 2035.
  The Director of Public Engagement and Director of Research and Messaging Files series contains the research, correspondence, meeting minutes, project files, and professional papers of Thalia Zepatos, Freedom to Marry's Director of Research and Messaging.
  The Director of Public Engagement and Director of Research and Messaging Files is organized in five groupings: National collaborative files, Civil marriage collaborative files, State files, Research, messaging, and public education projects, and Research files. These groupings are organized in the original order in which they were received.
  - National collaborative files, 2007-2009
    - Contract 10-10-10-20 plan, SC (Box 168, Folder 1)
    - FAQ and members (Box 168, Folder 2)
    - Grant summary, 2007-2009 (Box 168, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, 2008 April (Box 168, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, 2008 May (Box 168, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, 2008 December (Box 168, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, 2009 February (Box 168, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, 2009 September (Box 168, Folder 8)
    - 2009 post election debrief (Box 168, Folder 9)
    - Futures committee (Box 168, Folder 10)
    - Summary reports (Box 168, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 168, Folder 12)
  - Civil marriage collaborative files, 2009-2014
    - Meeting, 2009 June 9-2009 June 10 (Box 168, Folder 13)
    - Meeting, June 2010 (Box 169, Folder 1)
    - October 2010 meeting materials, 2010 October (Box 169, Folder 2)
    - November 2010 meeting materials, 2010 October (Box 169, Folder 3)
    - February 2011 meeting materials, 2011 February (Box 169, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, 2011 June (Box 169, Folder 5)
    - October 2011 meeting materials, 2011 October (Box 169, Folder 6)
    - February 2012 meeting materials, 2011 February (Box 169, Folder 7)
    - Priority states materials, 2011-2012 (Box 169, Folder 8)
    - State analysis, 2013-2014 (Box 169, Folder 9)
    - State briefing summary, 2012 October (Box 169, Folder 10)
    - Proposals and miscellaneous briefings (Box 169, Folder 11)
    - National landscape analysis and state targets (Box 169, Folder 12)
  - State files, 2006-2014
    - Arizona: No prop 107 (Box 169, Folder 13)
    - Colorado (Box 169, Folder 14)
    - California
      - Let California ring/plans (Box 169, Folder 15)
      - Let California Ring summer, 2008 (Box 169, Folder 16)
      - Jordan-Rustin coalition (Box 169, Folder 17)
      - Let California Ring partner propsals, 2008 (Box 169, Folder 18)
      - Let California Ring media buys (Box 169, Folder 19)
      - Decline to sign, 2008 (Box 169, Folder 20)
      - API Equality-Los Angeles (Box 169, Folder 21)
      - Prop 8 polls, circa 2008 (Box 170, Folder 1)
      - Equality for All campaign communication, circa 2008 (Box 170, Folder 2)
      - No prop 8 - const. outreach, circa 2008 (Box 170, Folder 3)
      - Prop 8 Equality for All plans, circa 2008 (Box 170, Folder 4)
      - E-day invisibility (Box 170, Folder 5)
      - Post prop 8, circa 2008 (Box 170, Folder 6)
    - Washington D.C. (Box 170, Folder 7)
    - Hawaii: Thomas W. (Box 170, Folder 8)
    - Iowa, 2008-2011 (Box 170, Folder 9-10)
    - Maine (Box 170, Folder 11)
    - Maryland, 2006-2010 (Box 170, Folder 12)
    - Michigan, 2008 (Box 170, Folder 13)
    - Minnesota
      - United S.C./Hire, 2011 (Box 170, Folder 14)
      - 2010-2011 (Box 171, Folder 1)
      - Freedom to Marry Minnesota PAC registration (Box 171, Folder 2)
      - Grove poll, 2012 January (Box 171, Folder 3)
    - New Jersey, 2008-2009 (Box 171, Folder 4)
    - New Mexico: Why Marriage Matters [WMM], 2013 (Box 171, Folder 5)
    - New Mexico: Equality New Mexico, 2014 (Box 171, Folder 6)
    - New York: original New York State incorporation Freedom to Marry Action 501(c)3, 2010 (Box 171, Folder 7)
    - Oregon, 2013-2014 (Box 171, Folder 8)
    - Rhode Island, 2010 (Box 171, Folder 9)
    - Washington C-3, 2012 (Box 171, Folder 10)
    - Washington camp, 2012 (Box 171, Folder 11)
    - Washington United, 2012 (Box 172, Folder 1)
  - Research, messaging, and public education projects, 2008-2014
    - Progress States, 2010-2014 (Box 172, Folder 2)
    - African American conference, 2008 (Box 172, Folder 3)
    - California - Let caring media buys, 2008 (Box 172, Folder 4)
    - California statewide Latinos, 2009 (Box 172, Folder 5)
    - One Iowa focus groups, 2008 (Box 172, Folder 6)
    - Freedom to Marry Start-up, 2009-2010 (Box 172, Folder 7)
    - Grove Fg's and research (Box 172, Folder 8)
    - Freedom to Marry grove research, 2010 (Box 172, Folder 9)
    - Questionnaires (Box 172, Folder 10)
    - National polls - marriage (Box 172, Folder 11)
    - Public education planning (Box 172, Folder 12)
    - Federal strategy/congress, 2011-2013 (Box 173, Folder 1)
    - Public education planning, 2010-2011 (Box 173, Folder 2)
    - Freedom to Marry institute Creating Change, 2009-2010 (Box 173, Folder 3)
    - Creating Change conference, 2011 (Box 173, Folder 4)
    - Let California Ring workshop Creating Change (Box 173, Folder 5)
    - Zepatos messaging powerpoint presentations, 2012-2014 (Box 173, Folder 6)
    - Moving Marriage Forward, 2012 (Box 173, Folder 7)
    - Thalia Zepetos presentation Minnesota, 2011 (Box 173, Folder 8)
    - Why Marriage Matters materials/messaging, 2012 (Box 173, Folder 9)
    - Polling guidelines for ballot, 2012 (Box 173, Folder 10)
    - Post prop 8 California research (Box 173, Folder 11)
    - Post 2012 evaluations/presentations, 2012-2013 (Box 173, Folder 12)
    - Maine post 2012 election poll (Box 173, Folder 13)
    - Anti-DOMA messaging, 2012 (Box 173, Folder 14)
    - Familia es Familia Latino message project, 2012-2015 (Box 173, Folder 15)
    - Familia plan, 2014 (Box 173, Folder 16)
    - Llego survey, 2004 (Box 174, Folder 1)
    - Colorado polling August, 2013 (Box 174, Folder 2)
    - Ottio survey, 2013 (Box 174, Folder 3)
    - Pew research, 2010-2014 (Box 174, Folder 4)
    - Third way (Box 174, Folder 5)
    - Other organizations, 2013 (Box 174, Folder 6)
  - Research files, 2005-2015
    - Evangelical research project, 2014-2015 (Box 175, Folder 1)
    - Oppo push-back advisory memos, 2011-2012 (Box 175, Folder 2)
    - Opposition push back research, 2011-2014 (Box 175, Folder 3)
    - "Harms Kids" research project notes and budgets, 2009-2012 (Box 175, Folder 4)
    - Apter/Herek studies, 2005-2008 (Box 175, Folder 5)
    - Analyst institute, 2010 (Box 175, Folder 6)
    - Ad shoot, 2011 November (Box 175, Folder 7)
    - Grove research kids pivot ad test, 2011 December (Box 175, Folder 8)
- Audiovisual materials, 1986-2013; Series VII; 30.74; 360 boxes
  The Audiovisual Materials series is comprised of television clips and segments (on VHS, DVD, and CD) concerning marriage equality. The bulk of this material was created by Freedom to Marry for television broadcast.
  The Audiovisual Materials series is comprised of four groupings: General, Evan Wolfson material, Freedom to Marry press clips, and Freedom to Marry produced material. These groupings are is organized alphabetically.
  Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy of non-commercially produced items for their personal use should consult the ordering reproductions information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
  Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.
  - General, 1989-2011
    - 1049 The Fight for Marriage Equality trailer total run time: 5:00 minutes Jim de Seve, 2001; 1 (Box 176)
    - 9BP 11-12 "Gays Converting Straights", 1 (Box 177)
    - A new youth-produced documentary brought to you by Children of Lesbians and Gays Everywhere youth leadership and action program "In My Shoes: Stories of Youth with LGBT Parents", 2005; 1 (Box 178)
    - A&E "Same Sex Marriages in America", 1 (Box 179)
    - ABA section of litigation annual conference, 2004 May 5-8; 1 (Box 180)
    - ABC Nightline "Rock Hudson Denial", 1 (Box 181)
    - ABC The View, 2006 October 26; 1 (Box 182)
    - ABC: Turning Point "Same Sex Marriages", 1 (Box 183)
    - American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU) of Hawaii Foundation "Constitutional Amendment" TV, 1996 April 19; 1 (Box 184)
    - Advertising gay marriage intiatives, 2004; 4 (Box 185–188)
      - Advertising gay marriage intiatives, 2016-M-0049-0128; 1 (Box 185)
      - Advertising gay marriage intiatives, 2016-M-0049-0129; 1 (Box 186)
      - Advertising gay marriage intiatives, 2016-M-0049-0130; 1 (Box 187)
      - Advertising gay marriage intiatives, 2016-M-0049-0127; 1 (Box 188)
    - "After We Win in Hawaii" marriage panel at Lavender Law, 1994 October 22; 1 (Box 189)
    - AIDS privacy/consumer survival, 1 (Box 190)
    - America Decides episode 6, 1 (Box 191)
    - American Political Science Association "Same-sex marriage and the 2004 election: Activists comment on what we did right and what we did wrong", Washington DC, 2005 September 1; 1 (Box 192)
    - Andersen v. King County Washington Supreme Court, Northwest Women's Law Center, Lambda Legal, American Civil Liberties Union-Washington (ACLU-WA), 2005 March 8; 1 (Box 193)
    - "Are Gay Rights Special Rights?" (Princeton), 1 (Box 194)
    - At Last! The First NY State Gay Wedding Reception LGBT center New York City DJ Ted Snowdon, 2011 July 24; 1 (Box 195)
    - Audio/video, 1 (Box 196)
    - B. Kerr F2 images, 2005 May 31; 1 (Box 197)
    - Balif dinner, 2003; 1 (Box 198)
    - Battle for Influence: Gay Marriage; presenter: Simon Cox producer: Richard Vadon, 1 (Box 199)
    - BBC Radio 4: Sunday programme BBC world service focus on faith, Hawaii marriage case, package only, no cue, 1 (Box 200)
    - Bev Smith Show Children of Gay Parents hour I, 2006 December 11; 1 (Box 201)
    - Bev Smith Show Children of Gay Parents hour II, 2006 December 11; 1 (Box 202)
    - "Blank?" Unidentified videos, 1 (Box 203)
    - "Blank?" unidentified videos, 1 (Box 204)
    - "Blank?" unidentified videos, 1 (Box 205)
    - "Blank?" unidentified videos, 1 (Box 206)
    - "Blank?" unidentified video, 1 (Box 207)
    - "Blank?" unidentified video, 1 (Box 208)
    - "Blank?" unidentified video, 1 (Box 209)
    - Bottom Line "Same Sex Marriages" AD: WBAL-TV, 1997 June 7; 1 (Box 210)
    - Bravo! TV (Toronto) "Marriage", 2003 November 22; 1 (Box 211)
    - CBS Sunday Morning "Gay Marriage", 1 (Box 212)
    - CBS This Morning "Anti-gay ads", 1 (Box 213)
    - CNBC, 1 (Box 214)
    - CNN Insight "Marriage in Canada", 2003 June 19; 1 (Box 215)
    - Columbus Ohio, press: MASS/THM/HB272, 1 (Box 216)
    - Constructing Change Topeka complete, 1996 April 6; 1 (Box 217)
    - Copy, 1 (Box 218)
    - Court TV "Legal Café", 1 (Box 219)
    - Court TV Air Check, 1993 April 30; 1 (Box 220)
    - Court TV Aircheck 7pm to 9pm, 1 (Box 221)
    - Court-TV Miller's Law 1: gay and lesbian marriages 2: school prayer millawooo9 - 10-11pm, 1993 May 12; 1 (Box 222)
    - CourtTV On Appeal #44 The Boy Scout Show Aired, 1998 August 10; 1 (Box 223)
    - CourtTV Rolanda, GMA, Dateline, etc. 011, 1996 October 10-1999 September 2; 1 (Box 224)
    - CourtTV Woodard, 1995 May; 1 (Box 225)
    - CourtTV Woodard v. Gallagher, 1 (Box 226)
    - Creating Change, 2010; 2 (Box 227–228)
      - Creating Change, 2016-M-0058-0005; 1 (Box 227)
      - Creating Change, 2016-M-0058-0006; 1 (Box 228)
    - CTV Air Check 5pm to 7pm, 4 (Box 229–232)
    - CTV Air check 7pm to 8pm, 1 (Box 233)
    - CTV air check 7pm to 9pm, 1 (Box 234)
    - CTV Aircheck, 1 (Box 235)
    - Democracy Now! "Skim-Milk Marriage", 1 (Box 236)
    - Democracy Now! Justice Department orders Florida to stop voter purge targeting Latino, Democratic voters; In victory for marriage equality, appeals court rules DOMA discriminates against same-sex couples; The OCCUPIED Amendment: Rep. Ted Deutch on banning corporate campaign money post-Citizens United; "Inside Job" director Charles Ferguson: where are the criminal prosecutions for financial crisis, 1 (Box 237)
    - Dialog show 379-019 "Same-Sex Marriage", 1997 January 10; 1 (Box 238)
    - Dialogue 80 with Pete Summers (WLAD, 800 AM) Topic: same-sex marriages. Guests: Ed Rose; Tom Kilgannon, director of communications for Christian Action Network, 1 (Box 239)
    - Diversity training: Third annual LGBT Workplace Awareness Training, presented by Evan Wolfson, of Freedom to Marry, Marla Hassner and Wazina Zondon of ESPA, 2009 June 29; 1 (Box 240)
    - Dohrn 6/56 WABC, 1 (Box 241)
    - "DOMA prohibited", 1 (Box 242)
    - Doric Wilson's Street Theater directed by Mark Finley, 1 (Box 243)
    - Education under fire presented by Amnesty International, 1 (Box 244)
    - EITB (Basque TV-Radio) "Olatz Arieta", 1 (Box 245)
    - Element Agency, 1 (Box 246)
    - Essay assignment 4:30 min, 2006 November; 1 (Box 247)
    - Every Family Matters Scott-Chung Basovich, 1 (Box 248)
    - Every Family Matters Scott-Chung Basovich (Box 249)